we've been given an array
each element is a string with two words
we need to turn this array into a new
array of strings
where each element is one word so we
know we want to do some transformation
here
and that tells us that we may want to
use the map
method so let's invoke map on our array
and we'll name our block parameter pairs
as we have pairs of words that will be
passed in
and we simply want to split
each pair of words into individual words
we can do that with the string split
method
without an argument this is simply going
to split on the white space
so let's first output this and see what
our array looks like now
so now we see a two-dimensional array
and each sub-array is an array of words
so we've successfully split our pairs of
words into single words
but we don't want a two-dimensional
array before we do anything else
let's reassign a to the return value
of this invocation of map
so now a points to this new
two-dimensional array
now as the problem description suggests
there is a very useful array method
to transform a multi-dimensional array
into a one-dimensional array
and that is the array method
so let's again reassign a to the return
value of invoking the flatten method
this method returns a new array which
will be one-dimensional
on line six will output a
and as you can see this one-dimensional
array contains
all of the elements that were in our
two-dimensional array
but it has simply flattened the array
from being
multi-dimensional into a one-dimensional
[Music]
array